$wt.dff={run:function(obj){obj.params=$wt.mergeParams({id:!1,lang:document.lang,official:$wt.languages.official},obj.params);if(!obj.params.id){console.log("WTINFO: Form tools, 'id' is missing!")}else{this.buildForm(obj)}
$wt.next(obj)},buildForm:function(obj){let placeholders=$wt.dictionary.dff[obj.params.lang]||$wt.dictionary.dff.en;placeholders.give_us=placeholders.give_us.replace(/<link>/ig,'<a href="#dff-helpusdesc">').replace(/<\/link>/g,'</a>');let lang=obj.params.lang||document.lang;let europe_direct_url="https://european-union.europa.eu/contact-eu_"+lang;placeholders.europe_direct=placeholders.europe_direct.replace(/<link>/ig,`<a class="wt-ecl-link" href="${europe_direct_url}" target="_blank">`).replace(/<\/link>/g,'</a>');placeholders.id=$wt.id();obj.innerHTML=$wt.template(['<form autocomplete="off" id="_{id}">','<div id="wt-dff--live" class="wt-dff--live" aria-live="polite" hidden="true"></div>',`<div class="wt-dff--choose">
        <fieldset class="wt-dff--rating" aria-labelledby="legend-id">
          <legend id="legend-id">{rate_this}</legend>
          <div class="wt-rating">
            <input type="radio" id="rate1" value="1" name="wt-rating"/>
            <label class="wt-rating--label" for="rate1">
              <span class="wt-offscreen">1 {star}</span>
            </label>
            <input type="radio" id="rate2" value="2" name="wt-rating"/>
            <label class="wt-rating--label" for="rate2">
              <span class="wt-offscreen">2 {stars}</span>
            </label>
            <input type="radio" id="rate3" value="3" name="wt-rating"/>
            <label class="wt-rating--label" for="rate3">
              <span class="wt-offscreen">3 {stars}</span>
            </label>
            <input type="radio" id="rate4" value="4" name="wt-rating"/>
            <label class="wt-rating--label" for="rate4">
              <span class="wt-offscreen">4 {stars}</span>
            </label>
            <input type="radio" id="rate5" value="5" name="wt-rating"/>
            <label class="wt-rating--label" for="rate5">
              <span class="wt-offscreen">5 {stars}</span>
            </label>
          </div>
          <div class="wt-dff--more-feedback">{give_us}</div>
        </fieldset>
      </div>`,`<div class="wt-dff--container-child wt-dff--options-list" hidden="true">
        <fieldset class="wt-ecl-form-group">
          <legend class="wt-ecl-form-label" id="dff-helpusdesc">{help_us}</legend>
          <div class="wt-ecl-radio">
            <input 
              id="cannot_find_info" 
              name="dff-options" 
              class="wt-ecl-radio__input" 
              type="radio" 
              value="cannot_find_info" 
              required="true" 
              aria-describedby="cannot_find_info"/>
            <label class="wt-ecl-radio__label" for="cannot_find_info">
              <span class="wt-ecl-radio__box">
                <span class="wt-ecl-radio__box-inner"></span>
              </span>
              <span class="wt-ecl-radio__text">{information_not_found}</span>
            </label>
          </div>
          <div class="wt-ecl-radio">
            <input 
              id="mistake_issue" 
              name="dff-options" 
              class="wt-ecl-radio__input" 
              type="radio" 
              value="mistake_issue" 
              required="true" 
              aria-describedby="mistake_issue"/>
            <label class="wt-ecl-radio__label" for="mistake_issue">
              <span class="wt-ecl-radio__box">
                <span class="wt-ecl-radio__box-inner"></span>
              </span>
              <span class="wt-ecl-radio__text">{spot_mistake}</span>
            </label>
          </div>
          <div class="wt-ecl-radio">
            <input 
              id="technical_issue" 
              name="dff-options" 
              class="wt-ecl-radio__input" 
              type="radio" 
              value="technical_issue" 
              required="true" 
              aria-describedby="technical_issue"/>
            <label class="wt-ecl-radio__label" for="technical_issue">
              <span class="wt-ecl-radio__box">
                <span class="wt-ecl-radio__box-inner"></span>
              </span>
              <span class="wt-ecl-radio__text">{technical_issue}</span>
            </label>
          </div>
          <div class="wt-ecl-radio">
            <input 
              id="other_issue" 
              name="dff-options" 
              class="wt-ecl-radio__input" 
              type="radio" 
              value="other_issue" 
              required="true" 
              aria-describedby="other_issue"/>
            <label class="wt-ecl-radio__label" for="other_issue">
              <span class="wt-ecl-radio__box">
                <span class="wt-ecl-radio__box-inner"></span>
              </span>
              <span class="wt-ecl-radio__text">{error_other}</span>
            </label>
          </div>
          <div>
            <p class="wt-dff--personal-information">${$wt.label("dff", "personal_information", obj.params.lang)}</p>
          </div>
        </fieldset>
      </div>`,`<div class="wt-dff--container-child wt-dff--options-container" hidden="true">`,`<div class="wt-dff--option" hidden="true">
        <p><b>{need_help}</b><br/>{europe_direct}</p>
        <label class="wt-ecl-form-label" for="wt-dff--textarea-{id}">{website_help}<small 
        class="wt-ecl-form-label__required" aria-hidden="true">*</small></label>
      </div>`,`<div class="wt-dff--option" hidden="true">
        <label class="wt-ecl-form-label" for="wt-dff--textarea-{id}">{mistake_notice}<small 
        class="wt-ecl-form-label__required" aria-hidden="true">*</small></label>
        <div class="wt-ecl-help-block">{mistake_thanks}</div>
      </div>`,`<div class="wt-dff--option" hidden="true">
        <label class="wt-ecl-form-label" for="wt-dff--textarea-{id}">{what_problem}<small 
        class="wt-ecl-form-label__required" aria-hidden="true">*</small></label>
        <div class="wt-ecl-help-block">{technical_details}</div>
      </div>`,`<div class="wt-dff--option" hidden="true">
        <label class="wt-ecl-form-label" for="wt-dff--textarea-{id}">{other_question}<small 
        class="wt-ecl-form-label__required" aria-hidden="true">*</small></label>
        <div class="wt-ecl-help-block">{other_desc} {other_presence}</div>
      </div>`,`<div class="wt-dff--textarea">
        <textarea 
          id="wt-dff--textarea-{id}"
          name="dff-feedback" 
          class="wt-ecl-text-area wt-ecl-text-area--l"
          rows="4" 
          required="true"
          maxlength="500"
        ></textarea>
        <div class="wt-dff--textarea-desc">
          <small aria-hidden="true">* {field_mandatory}</small>  
          <small aria-live="polite" aria-atomic="true"><span>500</span> {remaining}</small>
        </div>
      </div>`,`<div class="wt-dff--validation-container">
        <div class="wt-dff--captcha"></div>
        <button class="wt-ecl-button wt-ecl-button--primary" type="submit" disabled="true">
          {submit_feedback}
        </button>
      </div>`,`</div>`,'</form>'].join(''),placeholders);obj.classList.add('wt-offprint');this.events(obj)},events:function(obj){let form=obj.querySelector('form');let live=obj.querySelector("#wt-dff--live");let choose=obj.querySelector('.wt-dff--choose');let helpus=obj.querySelector('.wt-dff--options-list');let optionsList=obj.querySelector('.wt-dff--options-list');let options=obj.querySelectorAll('.wt-dff--option');let optionsContainer=obj.querySelector('.wt-dff--options-container');let ratingInput=obj.querySelectorAll('.wt-rating input');let giveUsFeedback=obj.querySelector('a');let captchaContainer=obj.querySelector('.wt-dff--captcha');let captchaReady=!1;let isKeyboard=!1;let submitButton=obj.querySelector('button[type="submit"]');let textarea=obj.querySelector('textarea');let textareaLive=obj.querySelector('small[aria-live] span');let slide;let audio;const showMessage=(type,message)=>{live.removeAttribute("hidden");live.innerHTML=`
        <div class="wt-ecl-notification wt-ecl-notification--${type}" role="alert">
          <span class="wt-icon--${type} wt-icon--l wt-ecl-notification__icon"></span>
          <div class="wt-ecl-notification__content">
            <button class="wt-ecl-button wt-ecl-button--ghost wt-ecl-notification__close" type="button">
              <span class="wt-ecl-button__container">
                <span class="wt-ecl-button__label">
                  ${$wt.label("dff", "close", obj.params.lang)}
                </span>
                <span class="wt-icon--close wt-icon--xs wt-ecl-button__icon wt-ecl-button__icon--after">
                </span>
              </span>
            </button>
            <div class="wt-ecl-notification__description">${message}</div>
          </div>
        </div>
      `;live.querySelector("button").onclick=()=>live.setAttribute("hidden",!0)};const send=(noCaptcha,silence)=>{live.setAttribute("hidden",!0);let toSend={subid:obj.querySelector("form").id,form_id:obj.params.id,rating:obj.querySelector('input[name="wt-rating"]:checked')?.value||0,encountered_problems:obj.querySelector('input[name="dff-options"]:checked')?.value||"",describe_problem:textarea?.value||"",url:location.href,referer:document.referrer,language:document.lang,wt_captcha_sid:obj.querySelector("input[name='wt_captcha_sid']")?.value||null,wt_captcha_answer:obj.querySelector("input[name='wt_captcha_answer']")?.value||null};if(noCaptcha){delete toSend.wt_captcha_sid;delete toSend.wt_captcha_answer}
if(silence){$wt.ajax({url:$wt.root+"/rest/dff/v2",data:toSend,success:()=>{},error:()=>{}});return}
$wt.ajax({url:$wt.root+"/rest/dff/v2",data:toSend,success:()=>{showMessage("success",$wt.label('dff','thank_you_message',obj.params.lang));choose.remove();helpus.remove();optionsContainer.remove()},error:()=>{if($wt.captcha){$wt.captcha.refresh()}
showMessage("error",$wt.label('dff','message_error_request',obj.params.lang))}})};const rate=(val)=>{if(val<5){clearTimeout($wt.dff.timer);$wt.dff.timer=setTimeout(()=>send(!0,!0),3000);return optionsList.removeAttribute('hidden')}
send(!0)};const checkFields=(e)=>{e.preventDefault();$wt.captcha.validate(res=>{if(res.status==="success"){send()}else{$wt.captcha.refresh();setTimeout(()=>$wt.captcha.statements('captchaError'),250)}});return!1};form.addEventListener("submit",checkFields);["onkeydown","onkeypress","focus","blur","onkeyup"].forEach(evt=>{textarea[evt]=()=>{let size=500-textarea.value.length;if(size<0){return}
textareaLive.innerHTML=size}});[...ratingInput].forEach(inp=>{inp.onchange=function(evt){if(isKeyboard){isKeyboard=!1;return}
rate(this.value)};inp.onkeydown=()=>{isKeyboard=!0;setTimeout(()=>isKeyboard=!1,250)};inp.onkeypress=function(evt){if(evt.key==="Enter"){isKeyboard=!0;rate(this.value)}}});giveUsFeedback.onclick=()=>optionsList.removeAttribute('hidden');[...helpus.querySelectorAll("input")].forEach((inp,ii)=>{inp.onchange=()=>{[...options].forEach((elm,i)=>{elm.setAttribute("hidden",!0);if(i===ii){elm.removeAttribute("hidden");optionsContainer.removeAttribute("hidden");if(!captchaReady){captchaReady=!0;window.addEventListener('wtCaptchaReady',()=>{slide=obj.querySelector('input[name="wt_captcha_slider_text"]');audio=obj.querySelector('input[name="wt_captcha_slider_audio"]');const toggleSubmitButton=()=>{submitButton.setAttribute('disabled',!0);if(slide.value!=='0'||audio.value!==''){submitButton.removeAttribute('disabled')}};slide.addEventListener("change",toggleSubmitButton);audio.addEventListener("change",toggleSubmitButton)},{once:!0});$wt.render(captchaContainer,{service:"captcha",lang:obj.params.lang||document.lang})}}})}})}};$wt.addTranslation({"dff":{"bg":{"rate_this":"\u041e\u0446\u0435\u043d\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0442\u0430\u0437\u0438 \u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0446\u0430","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"\u0438\u043b\u0438 <link>\u0438\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u0432\u043e\u0435\u0442\u043e \u043c\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435<\/link>","remaining":"\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0449\u0438 \u0437\u043d\u0430\u043a\u0430","need_help":"\u041d\u0443\u0436\u0434\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u0435 \u043e\u0442 \u043f\u043e\u043c\u043e\u0449, \u0437\u0430 \u0434\u0430 \u043d\u0430\u043c\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0442\u043e\u0432\u0430, \u043a\u043e\u0435\u0442\u043e \u0442\u044a\u0440\u0441\u0438\u0442\u0435?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435 \u0434\u0430 \u0432\u0438 \u043f\u043e\u043c\u043e\u0433\u043d\u0435 (\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0430\u0440\u044f \u0441\u0435 \u0432 \u043d\u043e\u0432 \u0442\u0430\u0431).","website_help":"\u0421\u043c\u044f\u0442\u0430\u0442\u0435 \u043b\u0438, \u0447\u0435 \u043b\u0438\u043f\u0441\u0432\u0430 \u0438\u043d\u0444\u043e\u0440\u043c\u0430\u0446\u0438\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u0442\u043e\u0437\u0438 \u0443\u0435\u0431\u0441\u0430\u0439\u0442 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u043d\u0430 \u0442\u0430\u0437\u0438 \u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0446\u0430? \u041a\u0430\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0438 \u043a\u0430\u043a\u0432\u043e \u0442\u0440\u044f\u0431\u0432\u0430 \u0434\u0430 \u0434\u043e\u0431\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043c.","mistake_notice":"\u041c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043b\u0438 \u0434\u0430 \u0434\u0430\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0447\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u0434\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438 \u0437\u0430 \u0433\u0440\u0435\u0448\u043a\u0438\u0442\u0435, \u043a\u043e\u0438\u0442\u043e \u0441\u0442\u0435 \u0437\u0430\u0431\u0435\u043b\u044f\u0437\u0430\u043b\u0438?","mistake_thanks":"\u0429\u0435 \u043f\u043e\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043c \u0433\u0440\u0435\u0448\u043a\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u044a\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e \u043d\u0430\u0439-\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e.","technical_details":"\u041c\u043e\u043b\u044f, \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u044a\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e \u043d\u0430\u0439-\u043c\u043d\u043e\u0433\u043e \u043f\u043e\u0434\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0438, \u0437\u0430 \u0434\u0430 \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043c \u0434\u0430 \u0440\u0435\u0448\u0438\u043c \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043b\u0435\u043c\u0430.","other_question":"\u041a\u0430\u043a\u0432\u043e \u0431\u0438\u0445\u0442\u0435 \u0438\u0441\u043a\u0430\u043b\u0438 \u0434\u0430 \u0441\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0441 \u043d\u0430\u0441?","other_desc":"\u041c\u043e\u043b\u044f, \u0438\u043c\u0430\u0439\u0442\u0435 \u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0432\u0438\u0434, \u0447\u0435 \u043d\u0435 \u043c\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043c \u0434\u0430 \u0440\u0430\u0437\u0433\u043b\u0435\u0436\u0434\u0430\u043c\u0435 \u043a\u043e\u043d\u043a\u0440\u0435\u0442\u043d\u0438 \u0432\u044a\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0438 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u0436\u0430\u043b\u0431\u0438 \u043f\u043e \u0442\u0435\u043c\u0438 \u0438\u043b\u0438 \u043f\u043e\u043b\u0438\u0442\u0438\u043a\u0438 \u043d\u0430 \u0415\u0421. ","other_presence":"\u041d\u0430\u0448\u0430\u0442\u0430 \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430 \u0438\u043c\u0430 \u0437\u0430 \u0446\u0435\u043b \u0441\u0430\u043c\u043e \u0434\u0430 \u043e\u043f\u0442\u0438\u043c\u0438\u0437\u0438\u0440\u0430 \u0434\u0438\u0433\u0438\u0442\u0430\u043b\u043d\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0430\u0441\u043f\u0435\u043a\u0442\u0438 \u043d\u0430 \u043e\u043d\u043b\u0430\u0439\u043d \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u044a\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435\u0442\u043e \u043d\u0430 \u041a\u043e\u043c\u0438\u0441\u0438\u044f\u0442\u0430.","help_us":"\u041f\u043e\u043c\u043e\u0433\u043d\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0438 \u0434\u0430 \u043f\u043e\u0434\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0438\u043c \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0430\u0442\u0430 \u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430 \u0441 \u0442\u043e\u0437\u0438 \u0441\u0430\u0439\u0442 \u2014 \u043a\u0430\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0438 \u043a\u0430\u043a\u0432\u0438 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043b\u0435\u043c\u0438 \u0441\u0440\u0435\u0449\u043d\u0430\u0445\u0442\u0435.","information_not_found":"\u041d\u0435 \u043d\u0430\u043c\u0438\u0440\u0430\u043c \u043d\u0443\u0436\u043d\u0430\u0442\u0430 \u0438\u043d\u0444\u043e\u0440\u043c\u0430\u0446\u0438\u044f","technical_issue":"\u0422\u0435\u0445\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043b\u0435\u043c","spot_mistake":"\u0413\u0440\u0435\u0448\u043a\u0430(\u0438) \u0432 \u0442\u0435\u043a\u0441\u0442\u0430","what_problem":"\u041a\u0430\u043a\u044a\u0432 \u0435 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043b\u0435\u043c\u044a\u0442?","error_other":"\u0414\u0440\u0443\u0433\u043e","submit_feedback":"\u0418\u0437\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u043d\u0435 \u043d\u0430 \u043a\u043e\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442\u0430\u0440","thank_you_message":"\u0411\u043b\u0430\u0433\u043e\u0434\u0430\u0440\u0438\u043c \u0432\u0438 \u0437\u0430 \u043a\u043e\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442\u0430\u0440\u0430!","message_error_request":"\u0412\u044a\u0437\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043d\u0430 \u0433\u0440\u0435\u0448\u043a\u0430 \u0438 \u043d\u0435 \u0443\u0441\u043f\u044f\u0445\u043c\u0435 \u0434\u0430 \u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u043c \u0432\u0430\u0448\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u043a\u043e\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442\u0430\u0440\u0438. \u041c\u043e\u043b\u044f, \u043e\u043f\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0439\u0442\u0435 \u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0432\u043e.","message_error_fields":"\u041c\u043e\u043b\u044f, \u043f\u043e\u043f\u044a\u043b\u043d\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u0432\u0441\u0438\u0447\u043a\u0438 \u043f\u043e\u043b\u0435\u0442\u0430, \u043e\u0441\u0432\u0435\u043d \u0430\u043a\u043e \u043d\u0435 \u0441\u0430 \u043e\u0442\u0431\u0435\u043b\u044f\u0437\u0430\u043d\u0438 \u043a\u0430\u0442\u043e \u043d\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0434\u044a\u043b\u0436\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043d\u0438.","close":"\u0417\u0430\u0442\u0432\u0430\u0440\u044f\u043d\u0435","tell_us":"\u041a\u0430\u0436\u0435\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0438 \u043a\u0430\u043a\u044a\u0432 \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043b\u0435\u043c \u0441\u0442\u0435 \u0438\u043c\u0430\u043b\u0438:","other":"\u0414\u0440\u0443\u0433\u043e","field_mandatory":"\u0422\u043e\u0432\u0430 \u043f\u043e\u043b\u0435 \u0435 \u0437\u0430\u0434\u044a\u043b\u0436\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043d\u043e","personal_information":"\u041c\u043e\u043b\u044f, \u043d\u0435 \u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0432\u0430\u0439\u0442\u0435 \u043d\u0438\u043a\u0430\u043a\u0432\u0438 \u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u0438 \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u0438 \u0432 \u043a\u043e\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442\u0430\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435 \u0441\u0438."},"cs":{"rate_this":"Ohodnotit tuto str\u00e1nku","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"nebo <link>Zaslat n\u00e1zor<\/link>","remaining":"po\u010det zb\u00fdvaj\u00edc\u00edch znak\u016f","need_help":"Pot\u0159ebujete pomoc p\u0159i hled\u00e1n\u00ed informac\u00ed?","europe_direct":"<link>S t\u00edm v\u00e1m m\u016f\u017ee pomoci slu\u017eba Europe Direct<\/link> (otev\u0159e se na nov\u00e9 kart\u011b).","website_help":"Domn\u00edv\u00e1te se, \u017ee na t\u011bchto str\u00e1nk\u00e1ch chyb\u00ed informace? Dejte n\u00e1m pros\u00edm v\u011bd\u011bt, co bychom m\u011bli doplnit.","mistake_notice":"M\u016f\u017eete pros\u00edm uv\u00e9st podrobnosti o chyb\u00e1ch, kter\u00e9 jste zaznamenali?","mistake_thanks":"Pokus\u00edme se je co nejd\u0159\u00edve opravit.","technical_details":"Uve\u010fte pros\u00edm co nejv\u00edce podrobnost\u00ed, abychom mohli probl\u00e9m vy\u0159e\u0161it.","other_question":"Chcete n\u00e1m n\u011bco sd\u011blit?","other_desc":"Nem\u016f\u017eeme se bohu\u017eel zab\u00fdvat konkr\u00e9tn\u00edmi ot\u00e1zkami ani st\u00ed\u017enostmi t\u00fdkaj\u00edc\u00edmi se z\u00e1le\u017eitost\u00ed nebo politiky EU. ","other_presence":"Na\u0161\u00edm \u00fakolem je pouze optimalizovat digit\u00e1ln\u00ed prezentaci Evropsk\u00e9 komise na internetu.","help_us":"Pokud ne, napi\u0161te n\u00e1m a my se vynasna\u017e\u00edme to napravit.","information_not_found":"neda\u0159\u00ed se mi naj\u00edt informace, kter\u00e9 pot\u0159ebuji","technical_issue":"technick\u00fd probl\u00e9m","spot_mistake":"chyby v textu","what_problem":"S jak\u00fdm probl\u00e9mem jste se setkali?","error_other":"jin\u00e1 mo\u017enost","submit_feedback":"Zaslat zp\u011btnou vazbu","thank_you_message":"D\u011bkujeme v\u00e1m za p\u0159ipom\u00ednky!","message_error_request":"Bohu\u017eel se vyskytla chyba a va\u0161i zp\u011btnou vazbu jsme nedostali.  Zkuste to pros\u00edm znovu.","message_error_fields":"Vypl\u0148te v\u0161echna pole (krom\u011b voliteln\u00fdch, kter\u00e1 mohou z\u016fstat pr\u00e1zdn\u00e1).","close":"Zav\u0159\u00edt","tell_us":"Uve\u010fte, s jak\u00fdm probl\u00e9mem se pot\u00fdk\u00e1te:","other":"jin\u00e9","field_mandatory":"Toto pole je povinn\u00e9","personal_information":"V koment\u00e1\u0159\u00edch neuv\u00e1d\u011bjte \u017e\u00e1dn\u00e9 osobn\u00ed \u00fadaje."},"da":{"rate_this":"Vurd\u00e9r denne side","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"eller <link>giv os mere feedback<\/link>","remaining":"tegn tilbage","need_help":"Har du brug for hj\u00e6lp til at finde det, du leder efter?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> kan hj\u00e6lpe dig med dette (\u00e5bner i en ny fane).","website_help":"Mener du, at der mangler informationer p\u00e5 dette websted eller denne side? Fort\u00e6l os, hvad vi skal tilf\u00f8je.","mistake_notice":"Kan du fort\u00e6lle mere om den eller de fejl, du har bem\u00e6rket?","mistake_thanks":"Vi vil rette fejlen\/fejlene s\u00e5 hurtigt som muligt.","technical_details":"Giv s\u00e5 mange informationer som muligt, s\u00e5 vi kan l\u00f8se problemet.","other_question":"Hvad vil du gerne fort\u00e6lle os?","other_desc":"V\u00e6r opm\u00e6rksom p\u00e5, at vi ikke kan besvare specifikke sp\u00f8rgsm\u00e5l eller behandle klager vedr\u00f8rende EU-anliggender eller -politikker. ","other_presence":"Vi har udelukkende til opgave at optimere de digitale aspekter af Kommissionens onlinetilstedev\u00e6relse.","help_us":"Hj\u00e6lp os med at forbedre din oplevelse \u2013 fort\u00e6l os om eventuelle problemer, du er st\u00f8dt p\u00e5.","information_not_found":"Jeg kan ikke finde de oplysninger, jeg har brug for","technical_issue":"Det er et teknisk problem","spot_mistake":"Der er fejl i teksten","what_problem":"Hvad er problemet?","error_other":"Andet","submit_feedback":"Indsend min feedback","thank_you_message":"Tak for din feedback!","message_error_request":"Der er opst\u00e5et en fejl, og vi har ikke modtaget din feedback. Pr\u00f8v igen senere.","message_error_fields":"Udfyld alle felterne, medmindre de er markeret som valgfrie.","close":"Luk","tell_us":"Fort\u00e6l os, hvilket problem du oplevede:","other":"Andet","field_mandatory":"Dette felt er obligatorisk","personal_information":"Undlad at afgive personlige oplysninger i dine kommentarer."},"de":{"rate_this":"Diese Seite bewerten","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"oder <link>Feedback geben<\/link>","remaining":"verbleibende Zeichen","need_help":"Wir helfen Ihnen suchen","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> ist Ihnen gern behilflich (\u00f6ffnet in einem anderen Fenster)","website_help":"Fehlen Informationen auf unserer Website oder auf dieser Seite? Sagen Sie uns, was Sie vermissen.","mistake_notice":"Welche Fehler sind Ihnen konkret aufgefallen?","mistake_thanks":"Wir werden sie schnellstm\u00f6glich korrigieren.","technical_details":"Bitte beschreiben Sie das Problem m\u00f6glichst genau, damit wir es l\u00f6sen k\u00f6nnen.","other_question":"Womit k\u00f6nnen wir Ihnen helfen?","other_desc":"Bitte beachten Sie, dass wir keine konkreten Fragen oder Beschwerden zur EU-Politik beantworten. ","other_presence":"Unsere Arbeit beschr\u00e4nkt sich auf die digitale Optimierung der Kommissions-Website.","help_us":"Helfen Sie uns, die Website zu verbessern! Auf welche Probleme sind Sie gesto\u00dfen?","information_not_found":"Informationen nicht gefunden","spot_mistake":"Fehler im Text","technical_issue":"Technische Probleme","what_problem":"Was ist das Problem?","error_other":"Sonstiges","submit_feedback":"Feedback abschicken","thank_you_message":"Vielen Dank f\u00fcr Ihr Feedback!","message_error_request":"Es ist ein Fehler aufgetreten. Wir konnten Ihr Feedback nicht verarbeiten. Bitte noch einmal versuchen.","close":"Schlie\u00dfen","tell_us":"Was hat nicht geklappt?","other":"Anderes Problem","field_mandatory":"Dies ist ein Pflichtfeld","personal_information":"Bitte machen Sie in Ihren Kommentaren keine personenbezogenen Angaben."},"et":{"rate_this":"Hinnake seda lehek\u00fclge","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"v\u00f5i <link>andke meile rohkem tagasisidet<\/link>","remaining":"t\u00e4hem\u00e4rki j\u00e4\u00e4nud","need_help":"Vajate abi otsitava teabe leidmiseks?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> saab teid aidata (avaneb uuel vahekaardil).","website_help":"Kas leiate, et sellel veebisaidil v\u00f5i sellel lehel puudub teatav teave? \u00d6elge meile, mida peaksime lisama.","mistake_notice":"Kas oskate esitada rohkem \u00fcksikasju t\u00e4heldatud vea (vigade) kohta?","mistake_thanks":"Parandame vea(d) v\u00f5imalikult kiiresti.","technical_details":"Palun esitage v\u00f5imalikult palju \u00fcksikasju, et saaksime probleemi lahendada.","other_question":"Mida sooviksite meiega jagada?","other_desc":"Pidage meeles, et me ei saa k\u00e4sitleda konkreetseid k\u00fcsimusi v\u00f5i kaebusi ELi asjade v\u00f5i poliitika kohta. ","other_presence":"Meie t\u00f6\u00f6 eesm\u00e4rk on lihtsalt optimeerida komisjoni veebip\u00f5hise kohaloleku digitaalseid aspekte.","help_us":"Aidake meil oma kogemust parandada - andke meile teada probleemidest, mida kogesite.","information_not_found":"Ma ei leia vajalikku teavet","technical_issue":"Tehniline k\u00fcsimus","spot_mistake":"Viga (vead) tekstis","what_problem":"Milles probleem seisneb?","error_other":"Muu","submit_feedback":"Esita minu tagasiside","thank_you_message":"T\u00e4name tagasiside eest!","message_error_request":"Ilmnes viga ja me ei saanud Teie tagasisidet. Palun proovige uuesti.","message_error_fields":"Palun t\u00e4itke k\u00f5ik v\u00e4ljad, mis ei ole m\u00e4rgitud valikulisteks.","close":"Sulge","tell_us":"Kirjeldage meile oma probleemi","other":"Muu","field_mandatory":"See v\u00e4li on kohustuslik","personal_information":"Palun \u00e4rge lisage oma kommentaaridesse isikuandmeid."},"el":{"rate_this":"\u0391\u03be\u03b9\u03bf\u03bb\u03bf\u03b3\u03ae\u03c3\u03c4\u03b5 \u03b1\u03c5\u03c4\u03ae \u03c4\u03b7 \u03c3\u03b5\u03bb\u03af\u03b4\u03b1","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"\u03ae <link>\u03c5\u03c0\u03bf\u03b2\u03ac\u03bb\u03b5\u03c4\u03b5 \u03c0\u03b5\u03c1\u03b9\u03c3\u03c3\u03cc\u03c4\u03b5\u03c1\u03b5\u03c2 \u03c0\u03b1\u03c1\u03b1\u03c4\u03b7\u03c1\u03ae\u03c3\u03b5\u03b9\u03c2<\/link>","remaining":"\u03b5\u03bd\u03b1\u03c0\u03bf\u03bc\u03ad\u03bd\u03bf\u03bd\u03c4\u03b5\u03c2 \u03c7\u03b1\u03c1\u03b1\u03ba\u03c4\u03ae\u03c1\u03b5\u03c2","need_help":"\u03a7\u03c1\u03b5\u03b9\u03ac\u03b6\u03b5\u03c3\u03c4\u03b5 \u03b2\u03bf\u03ae\u03b8\u03b5\u03b9\u03b1 \u03b3\u03b9\u03b1 \u03bd\u03b1 \u03b2\u03c1\u03b5\u03af\u03c4\u03b5 \u03b1\u03c5\u03c4\u03cc \u03c0\u03bf\u03c5 \u03c8\u03ac\u03c7\u03bd\u03b5\u03c4\u03b5;","europe_direct":"<link>\u0397 \u03c5\u03c0\u03b7\u03c1\u03b5\u03c3\u03af\u03b1 Europe Direct<\/link>\u03bc\u03c0\u03bf\u03c1\u03b5\u03af \u03bd\u03b1 \u03c3\u03b1\u03c2 \u03b2\u03bf\u03b7\u03b8\u03ae\u03c3\u03b5\u03b9 \u03c3\u03c4\u03b7\u03bd \u03b1\u03bd\u03b1\u03b6\u03ae\u03c4\u03b7\u03c3\u03ae \u03c3\u03b1\u03c2 (\u03b1\u03bd\u03bf\u03af\u03b3\u03b5\u03b9 \u03c3\u03b5 \u03bd\u03ad\u03b1 \u03ba\u03b1\u03c1\u03c4\u03ad\u03bb\u03b1).","website_help":"\u0398\u03b5\u03c9\u03c1\u03b5\u03af\u03c4\u03b5 \u03cc\u03c4\u03b9 \u03bb\u03b5\u03af\u03c0\u03bf\u03c5\u03bd \u03c0\u03bb\u03b7\u03c1\u03bf\u03c6\u03bf\u03c1\u03af\u03b5\u03c2 \u03c3\u2019 \u03b1\u03c5\u03c4\u03cc\u03bd \u03c4\u03bf\u03bd \u03b9\u03c3\u03c4\u03cc\u03c4\u03bf\u03c0\u03bf \u03ae \u03c3\u2019 \u03b1\u03c5\u03c4\u03ae \u03c4\u03b7 \u03c3\u03b5\u03bb\u03af\u03b4\u03b1; \u03a0\u03b5\u03af\u03c4\u03b5 \u03bc\u03b1\u03c2 \u03c4\u03b9 \u03c0\u03c1\u03ad\u03c0\u03b5\u03b9 \u03bd\u03b1 \u03c0\u03c1\u03bf\u03c3\u03b8\u03ad\u03c3\u03bf\u03c5\u03bc\u03b5.","mistake_notice":"\u039c\u03c0\u03bf\u03c1\u03b5\u03af\u03c4\u03b5 \u03bd\u03b1 \u03b4\u03ce\u03c3\u03b5\u03c4\u03b5 \u03c0\u03b5\u03c1\u03b9\u03c3\u03c3\u03cc\u03c4\u03b5\u03c1\u03b5\u03c2 \u03bb\u03b5\u03c0\u03c4\u03bf\u03bc\u03ad\u03c1\u03b5\u03b9\u03b5\u03c2 \u03b3\u03b9\u03b1 \u03c4\u03bf \u03bb\u03ac\u03b8\u03bf\u03c2 \u03ae \u03c4\u03b1 \u03bb\u03ac\u03b8\u03b7 \u03c0\u03bf\u03c5 \u03b5\u03bd\u03c4\u03bf\u03c0\u03af\u03c3\u03b1\u03c4\u03b5;","mistake_thanks":"\u0398\u03b1 \u03b4\u03b9\u03bf\u03c1\u03b8\u03ce\u03c3\u03bf\u03c5\u03bc\u03b5 \u03c4\u03bf \u03bb\u03ac\u03b8\u03bf\u03c2\/\u03c4\u03b1 \u03bb\u03ac\u03b8\u03b7 \u03c4\u03bf \u03c3\u03c5\u03bd\u03c4\u03bf\u03bc\u03cc\u03c4\u03b5\u03c1\u03bf \u03b4\u03c5\u03bd\u03b1\u03c4\u03cc\u03bd.","technical_details":"\u03a0\u03b1\u03c1\u03b1\u03ba\u03b1\u03bb\u03b5\u03af\u03c3\u03b8\u03b5 \u03bd\u03b1 \u03c0\u03b1\u03c1\u03ac\u03c3\u03c7\u03b5\u03c4\u03b5 \u03cc\u03c3\u03bf \u03c4\u03bf \u03b4\u03c5\u03bd\u03b1\u03c4\u03cc\u03bd \u03c0\u03b5\u03c1\u03b9\u03c3\u03c3\u03cc\u03c4\u03b5\u03c1\u03b5\u03c2 \u03bb\u03b5\u03c0\u03c4\u03bf\u03bc\u03ad\u03c1\u03b5\u03b9\u03b5\u03c2 \u03ce\u03c3\u03c4\u03b5 \u03bd\u03b1 \u03bc\u03c0\u03bf\u03c1\u03ad\u03c3\u03bf\u03c5\u03bc\u03b5 \u03bd\u03b1 \u03bb\u03cd\u03c3\u03bf\u03c5\u03bc\u03b5 \u03c4\u03bf \u03b6\u03ae\u03c4\u03b7\u03bc\u03b1.","other_question":"\u03a4\u03b9 \u03b8\u03b1 \u03b8\u03ad\u03bb\u03b1\u03c4\u03b5 \u03bd\u03b1 \u03bc\u03bf\u03b9\u03c1\u03b1\u03c3\u03c4\u03b5\u03af\u03c4\u03b5 \u03bc\u03b1\u03b6\u03af \u03bc\u03b1\u03c2;","other_desc":"\u0395\u03c0\u03b9\u03c3\u03b7\u03bc\u03b1\u03af\u03bd\u03bf\u03c5\u03bc\u03b5 \u03cc\u03c4\u03b9 \u03b4\u03b5\u03bd \u03bc\u03c0\u03bf\u03c1\u03bf\u03cd\u03bc\u03b5 \u03bd\u03b1 \u03c7\u03b5\u03b9\u03c1\u03b9\u03c3\u03c4\u03bf\u03cd\u03bc\u03b5 \u03c3\u03c5\u03b3\u03ba\u03b5\u03ba\u03c1\u03b9\u03bc\u03ad\u03bd\u03b5\u03c2 \u03b5\u03c1\u03c9\u03c4\u03ae\u03c3\u03b5\u03b9\u03c2 \u03ae \u03ba\u03b1\u03c4\u03b1\u03b3\u03b3\u03b5\u03bb\u03af\u03b5\u03c2 \u03c3\u03c7\u03b5\u03c4\u03b9\u03ba\u03ac \u03bc\u03b5 \u03b8\u03ad\u03bc\u03b1\u03c4\u03b1 \u03ae \u03c0\u03bf\u03bb\u03b9\u03c4\u03b9\u03ba\u03ad\u03c2 \u03c4\u03b7\u03c2 \u0395\u0395. ","other_presence":"\u03a4\u03bf \u03ad\u03c1\u03b3\u03bf \u03bc\u03b1\u03c2 \u03b1\u03c0\u03bf\u03c3\u03ba\u03bf\u03c0\u03b5\u03af \u03b1\u03c0\u03bb\u03ce\u03c2 \u03c3\u03c4\u03b7 \u03b2\u03b5\u03bb\u03c4\u03b9\u03c3\u03c4\u03bf\u03c0\u03bf\u03af\u03b7\u03c3\u03b7 \u03c4\u03c9\u03bd \u03c8\u03b7\u03c6\u03b9\u03b1\u03ba\u03ce\u03bd \u03c0\u03c4\u03c5\u03c7\u03ce\u03bd \u03c4\u03b7\u03c2 \u03b4\u03b9\u03b1\u03b4\u03b9\u03ba\u03c4\u03c5\u03b1\u03ba\u03ae\u03c2 \u03c0\u03b1\u03c1\u03bf\u03c5\u03c3\u03af\u03b1\u03c2 \u03c4\u03b7\u03c2 \u0395\u03c0\u03b9\u03c4\u03c1\u03bf\u03c0\u03ae\u03c2.","help_us":"\u0392\u03bf\u03b7\u03b8\u03ae\u03c3\u03c4\u03b5 \u03bc\u03b1\u03c2 \u03bd\u03b1 \u03b2\u03b5\u03bb\u03c4\u03b9\u03ce\u03c3\u03bf\u03c5\u03bc\u03b5 \u03c4\u03b7\u03bd \u03b5\u03bc\u03c0\u03b5\u03b9\u03c1\u03af\u03b1 \u03c3\u03b1\u03c2 \u2014 \u03c0\u03b5\u03af\u03c4\u03b5 \u03bc\u03b1\u03c2 \u03c4\u03c5\u03c7\u03cc\u03bd \u03c0\u03c1\u03bf\u03b2\u03bb\u03ae\u03bc\u03b1\u03c4\u03b1 \u03c0\u03bf\u03c5 \u03b1\u03bd\u03c4\u03b9\u03bc\u03b5\u03c4\u03c9\u03c0\u03af\u03c3\u03b1\u03c4\u03b5.","information_not_found":"\u0394\u03b5\u03bd \u03bc\u03c0\u03bf\u03c1\u03ce \u03bd\u03b1 \u03b2\u03c1\u03c9 \u03c4\u03b1 \u03c3\u03c4\u03bf\u03b9\u03c7\u03b5\u03af\u03b1 \u03c0\u03bf\u03c5 \u03c7\u03c1\u03b5\u03b9\u03ac\u03b6\u03bf\u03bc\u03b1\u03b9","technical_issue":"\u03a4\u03b5\u03c7\u03bd\u03b9\u03ba\u03cc \u03b6\u03ae\u03c4\u03b7\u03bc\u03b1","spot_mistake":"\u039b\u03ac\u03b8\u03bf\u03c2\/-\u03b7 \u03c3\u03c4\u03bf \u03ba\u03b5\u03af\u03bc\u03b5\u03bd\u03bf","what_problem":"\u03a0\u03bf\u03b9\u03bf \u03c6\u03b1\u03af\u03bd\u03b5\u03c4\u03b1\u03b9 \u03bd\u03b1 \u03b5\u03af\u03bd\u03b1\u03b9 \u03c4\u03bf \u03c0\u03c1\u03cc\u03b2\u03bb\u03b7\u03bc\u03b1;","error_other":"\u0386\u03bb\u03bb\u03bf","submit_feedback":"\u03a5\u03c0\u03bf\u03b2\u03bf\u03bb\u03ae \u03c4\u03c9\u03bd \u03c0\u03b1\u03c1\u03b1\u03c4\u03b7\u03c1\u03ae\u03c3\u03b5\u03ce\u03bd \u03bc\u03bf\u03c5","thank_you_message":"\u03a3\u03b1\u03c2 \u03b5\u03c5\u03c7\u03b1\u03c1\u03b9\u03c3\u03c4\u03bf\u03cd\u03bc\u03b5 \u03b3\u03b9\u03b1 \u03c4\u03b9\u03c2 \u03c0\u03b1\u03c1\u03b1\u03c4\u03b7\u03c1\u03ae\u03c3\u03b5\u03b9\u03c2 \u03c3\u03b1\u03c2!","message_error_request":"\u03a0\u03b1\u03c1\u03bf\u03c5\u03c3\u03b9\u03ac\u03c3\u03c4\u03b7\u03ba\u03b5 \u03c3\u03c6\u03ac\u03bb\u03bc\u03b1 \u03ba\u03b1\u03b9 \u03b4\u03b5\u03bd \u03ba\u03b1\u03c4\u03ad\u03c3\u03c4\u03b7 \u03b4\u03c5\u03bd\u03b1\u03c4\u03cc\u03bd \u03bd\u03b1 \u03bb\u03ac\u03b2\u03bf\u03c5\u03bc\u03b5 \u03c4\u03b9\u03c2 \u03c0\u03b1\u03c1\u03b1\u03c4\u03b7\u03c1\u03ae\u03c3\u03b5\u03b9\u03c2 \u03c3\u03b1\u03c2. \u03a0\u03c1\u03bf\u03c3\u03c0\u03b1\u03b8\u03ae\u03c3\u03c4\u03b5 \u03c0\u03ac\u03bb\u03b9.","message_error_fields":"\u03a3\u03c5\u03bc\u03c0\u03bb\u03b7\u03c1\u03ce\u03c3\u03c4\u03b5 \u03cc\u03bb\u03b1 \u03c4\u03b1 \u03c0\u03b5\u03b4\u03af\u03b1, \u03b5\u03ba\u03c4\u03cc\u03c2 \u03b5\u03ac\u03bd \u03b5\u03c0\u03b9\u03c3\u03b7\u03bc\u03b1\u03af\u03bd\u03bf\u03bd\u03c4\u03b1\u03b9 \u03c9\u03c2 \u03c0\u03c1\u03bf\u03b1\u03b9\u03c1\u03b5\u03c4\u03b9\u03ba\u03ac","close":"\u039a\u03bb\u03b5\u03af\u03c3\u03b9\u03bc\u03bf","tell_us":"\u03a0\u03b5\u03af\u03c4\u03b5 \u03bc\u03b1\u03c2 \u03c4\u03b9 \u03c0\u03c1\u03cc\u03b2\u03bb\u03b7\u03bc\u03b1 \u03b1\u03bd\u03c4\u03b9\u03bc\u03b5\u03c4\u03c9\u03c0\u03af\u03c3\u03b1\u03c4\u03b5:","other":"\u0386\u03bb\u03bb\u03bf","field_mandatory":"\u03a4\u03bf \u03c0\u03b5\u03b4\u03af\u03bf \u03b1\u03c5\u03c4\u03cc \u03b5\u03af\u03bd\u03b1\u03b9 \u03c5\u03c0\u03bf\u03c7\u03c1\u03b5\u03c9\u03c4\u03b9\u03ba\u03cc","personal_information":"\u03a0\u03b1\u03c1\u03b1\u03ba\u03b1\u03bb\u03b5\u03af\u03c3\u03c4\u03b5 \u03bd\u03b1 \u03bc\u03b7 \u03c3\u03c5\u03bc\u03c0\u03b5\u03c1\u03b9\u03bb\u03ac\u03b2\u03b5\u03c4\u03b5 \u03c3\u03c4\u03b9\u03c2 \u03b1\u03c0\u03b1\u03bd\u03c4\u03ae\u03c3\u03b5\u03b9\u03c2 \u03c3\u03b1\u03c2 \u03b4\u03b5\u03b4\u03bf\u03bc\u03ad\u03bd\u03b1 \u03c0\u03c1\u03bf\u03c3\u03c9\u03c0\u03b9\u03ba\u03bf\u03cd \u03c7\u03b1\u03c1\u03b1\u03ba\u03c4\u03ae\u03c1\u03b1."},"en":{"rate_this":"Rate this page","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"or <link>give us more feedback<\/link>","remaining":"characters remaining","need_help":"Need help to find what you\u2019re looking for?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> can help you with this (opens in a new tab).","website_help":"Do you feel information is missing on this site or this page? Tell us what we should add.","mistake_notice":"Can you give more details of the mistake(s) you noticed?","mistake_thanks":"We will correct the mistake(s) as soon as possible.","technical_details":"Please provide as many details as possible so that we can solve the issue.","other_question":"What would you like to share with us?","other_desc":"Please be aware that we cannot handle specific questions or complaints about EU affairs or policies. ","other_presence":"Our work aims simply to optimise the digital aspects of the Commission\u2019s online presence.","help_us":"Help us improve your experience \u2013 tell us any problems you had.","information_not_found":"Can\u2019t find the information I need","spot_mistake":"Mistake(s) in the text","technical_issue":"Technical issue","what_problem":"What seems to be the problem?","error_other":"Other","submit_feedback":"Submit my feedback","thank_you_message":"Thanks for your feedback!","message_error_request":"An error has occurred and we were unable to receive your feedback. Please try again.","close":"Close","tell_us":"Tell us what problem you had:","other":"Other","field_mandatory":"This field is mandatory","personal_information":"Please do not include any personal information in your comments."},"es":{"rate_this":"Califique esta p\u00e1gina","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"o <link>denos m\u00e1s informaci\u00f3n<\/link>","remaining":"caracteres restantes","need_help":"\u00bfNecesita ayuda para encontrar lo que busca?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> puede ayudarle (se abre en una nueva pesta\u00f1a).","website_help":"\u00bfCree que falta informaci\u00f3n en este sitio o en esta p\u00e1gina? D\u00edganos lo que deber\u00edamos a\u00f1adir.","mistake_notice":"\u00bfPuede darnos m\u00e1s detalles sobre el error o los errores que ha encontrado?","mistake_thanks":"Los corregiremos lo antes posible.","technical_details":"Facil\u00edtenos toda la informaci\u00f3n posible para que podamos resolverlo.","other_question":"\u00bfQu\u00e9 le gustar\u00eda comunicarnos?","other_desc":"Tenga en cuenta que no podemos gestionar preguntas o quejas espec\u00edficas sobre asuntos o pol\u00edticas de la UE. ","other_presence":"Nuestro trabajo consiste \u00fanicamente en mejorar los aspectos digitales de la presencia en l\u00ednea de la Comisi\u00f3n.","help_us":"Ay\u00fadenos a mejorar su experiencia. D\u00edganos los problemas que haya tenido.","information_not_found":"No encuentro la informaci\u00f3n que necesito","technical_issue":"Problema t\u00e9cnico","spot_mistake":"Error(es) en el texto","what_problem":"\u00bfEn qu\u00e9 consiste el problema?","error_other":"Otros","submit_feedback":"Enviar mis comentarios","thank_you_message":"\u00a1Gracias!","message_error_request":"Se ha producido un error y no hemos podido recibir sus observaciones. Int\u00e9ntelo de nuevo.","message_error_fields":"Rellene todos los campos, a menos que est\u00e9n marcados como opcionales.","close":"Cerrar","tell_us":"D\u00edganos qu\u00e9 problema ha tenido:","other":"Otro","field_mandatory":"Este campo es obligatorio","personal_information":"No incluya datos personales en sus comentarios."},"fr":{"rate_this":"\u00c9valuez cette page","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"ou <link>donnez-nous un avis plus d\u00e9taill\u00e9<\/link>","remaining":"caract\u00e8res restants","need_help":"Besoin d\u2019aide pour trouver une information?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> peut vous aider (s\u2019ouvre dans un nouvel onglet).","website_help":"Estimez-vous qu\u2019il manque des informations sur ce site ou cette page? Dites-nous ce que nous devrions ajouter.","mistake_notice":"Pouvez-vous donner plus de d\u00e9tails sur la ou les erreurs que vous avez remarqu\u00e9e(s)?","mistake_thanks":"Nous corrigerons dans les meilleurs d\u00e9lais.","technical_details":"Veuillez fournir le plus de d\u00e9tails possible afin que nous puissions r\u00e9soudre le probl\u00e8me.","other_question":"Que souhaitez-vous nous communiquer?","other_desc":"Veuillez noter que nous ne pouvons pas r\u00e9pondre \u00e0 des questions ou plaintes sp\u00e9cifiques concernant les politiques de l\u2019UE. ","other_presence":"Notre travail vise simplement \u00e0 optimiser les aspects num\u00e9riques de la pr\u00e9sence en ligne de la Commission.","help_us":"Aidez-nous \u00e0 am\u00e9liorer votre exp\u00e9rience: faites-nous part des probl\u00e8mes que vous avez rencontr\u00e9s.","information_not_found":"Je ne trouve pas l\u2019information que je cherche","technical_issue":"Probl\u00e8me technique","spot_mistake":"Erreur(s) dans le texte","what_problem":"Quel(s) probl\u00e8me(s) avez-vous rencontr\u00e9?","error_other":"Autre","submit_feedback":"Envoyer","thank_you_message":"Merci pour votre contribution!","message_error_request":"Une erreur s\u2019est produite: nous n\u2019avons pas pu recevoir votre avis. Veuillez r\u00e9essayer.","message_error_fields":"Veuillez remplir tous les champs, sauf ceux qui sont indiqu\u00e9s comme facultatifs.","close":"Fermer","tell_us":"Pr\u00e9cisez le probl\u00e8me que vous avez rencontr\u00e9:","other":"Autres","field_mandatory":"Ce champ est obligatoire","personal_information":"Veuillez ne pas introduire d\u2019informations \u00e0 caract\u00e8re personnel dans vos commentaires."},"ga":{"rate_this":"R\u00e1t\u00e1il an leathanach seo","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"n\u00f3 <link>tabhair tuilleadh aiseolais d\u00fainn<\/link>","remaining":"carachtar f\u00e1gtha","need_help":"An bhfuil cabhair uait chun teacht ar an m\u00e9id at\u00e1 uait?","europe_direct":"<link>Is f\u00e9idir le Europe Direct<\/link> cuidi\u00fa leat leis an m\u00e9id sin (oscla\u00edonn s\u00e9 i dt\u00e1b nua).","website_help":"An gceapann t\u00fa go bhfuil eolas ar iarraidh ar an su\u00edomh n\u00f3 ar an leathanach seo? Inis d\u00fainn faoin m\u00e9id is ceart d\u00fainn a chur leis.","mistake_notice":"An f\u00e9idir leat tuilleadh sonra\u00ed a thabhairt faoin mbot\u00fan n\u00f3 faoi na bot\u00fain a thug t\u00fa faoi deara?","mistake_thanks":"Ceart\u00f3imid an bot\u00fan n\u00f3 na bot\u00fain sin a luaithe is f\u00e9idir.","technical_details":"Tabhair a oiread sonra\u00ed agus is f\u00e9idir ionas gur f\u00e9idir linn an fhadhb a r\u00e9iteach.","other_question":"Cad ba mhaith leat a chomhroinnt linn?","other_desc":"Tabhair do d\u2019aire nach f\u00e9idir linn ceisteanna sonracha n\u00e1 gear\u00e1in shonracha faoi ghn\u00f3tha\u00ed n\u00e1 faoi bheartais an Aontais a l\u00e1imhse\u00e1il. ","other_presence":"Is \u00e9 is aidhm d\u00e1r gcuid oibre an leas is fearr is f\u00e9idir a bhaint as na gn\u00e9ithe digiteacha a bhaineann le l\u00e1ithreacht an Choimisi\u00fain ar l\u00edne.","help_us":"Cuidigh linn feabhas a chur ar d\u2019eisp\u00e9ireas \u2013 inis d\u00fainn faoi aon fhadhbanna a bh\u00ed agat.","information_not_found":"N\u00ed f\u00e9idir liom teacht ar an eolas a theasta\u00edonn uaim","technical_issue":"Fadhb theicni\u00fail","spot_mistake":"Bot\u00fan n\u00f3 bot\u00fain sa t\u00e9acs","what_problem":"Cad \u00e9 an fhadhb at\u00e1 ann?","error_other":"Eile","submit_feedback":"Seol isteach mo chuid aiseolais","thank_you_message":"Go raibh maith agat as an aiseolas a thabhairt!","message_error_request":"Tharla earr\u00e1id agus n\u00ed rabhamar in ann do chuid aiseolais a fh\u00e1il. Bain triail as ar\u00eds.","message_error_fields":"L\u00edon isteach na r\u00e9ims\u00ed uile, ach amh\u00e1in m\u00e1 t\u00e1 siad marc\u00e1ilte mar r\u00e9ims\u00ed roghnacha.","close":"D\u00fan","tell_us":"Inis d\u00fainn faoin bhfadhb a bh\u00ed agat:","other":"Eile","field_mandatory":"T\u00e1 an r\u00e9imse seo \u00e9igeantach","personal_information":"N\u00e1 cuir isteach sonra\u00ed pearsanta d\u2019aon chine\u00e1l i do chuid bar\u00falacha."},"hr":{"rate_this":"Ocijenite ovu stranicu","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"ili nam <link>po\u0161aljite svoje komentare<\/link>","remaining":"Broj preostalih znakova:","need_help":"Ne uspijevate prona\u0107i to \u0161to tra\u017eite?","europe_direct":"S time vam mo\u017ee pomo\u0107i <link>Europe Direct<\/link> (poveznica \u0107e se otvoriti u novoj kartici).","website_help":"Smatrate da na ovom portalu ili ovoj stranici neke informacije nedostaju? Recite nam \u0161to bismo trebali dodati.","mistake_notice":"Mo\u017eete li podrobnije opisati pogre\u0161ke koje ste uo\u010dili?","mistake_thanks":"Nastojat \u0107emo ih \u0161to br\u017ee ispraviti.","technical_details":"Poku\u0161ajte \u0161to detaljnije opisati problem kako bismo ga lak\u0161e rije\u0161ili.","other_question":"\u017delite s nama podijeliti svoje komentare?","other_desc":"Napominjemo da ne mo\u017eemo odgovarati na konkretna pitanja ili pritu\u017ebe u vezi s poslovima ili politikama EU-a. ","other_presence":"Zadu\u017eeni smo samo za digitalne aspekte Komisijine prisutnosti na internetu.","help_us":"Pomognite nam da je pobolj\u0161amo! Na koje ste probleme nai\u0161li?","information_not_found":"ne mogu prona\u0107i potrebne informacije","technical_issue":"tehni\u010dki problem","spot_mistake":"tekst sadr\u017eava pogre\u0161ke","what_problem":"U \u010demu je problem?","error_other":"Ostalo","submit_feedback":"Po\u0161alji","thank_you_message":"Hvala na povratnim informacijama!","message_error_request":"Do\u0161lo je do pogre\u0161ke. Nismo primili povratne informacije. Poku\u0161ajte ponovno.","message_error_fields":"Ispunite sva polja koja nisu ozna\u010dena kao neobvezna.","close":"Zatvori","tell_us":"Ozna\u010dite na kakav ste problem nai\u0161li:","other":"ne\u0161to drugo","field_mandatory":"Ovo je polje obvezno","personal_information":"Molimo da u svojim komentarima ne navodite osobne podatke."},"it":{"rate_this":"Valuta questa pagina","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"oppure <link>invia altro feedback<\/link>","remaining":"caratteri rimanenti","need_help":"Serve aiuto per trovare ci\u00f2 che cerchi?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> pu\u00f2 darti una mano (si apre in una nuova scheda).","website_help":"Ritieni che su questo sito o pagina manchino informazioni? Specifica cosa dovremmo aggiungere.","mistake_notice":"Puoi fornire maggiori dettagli sugli errori rilevati?","mistake_thanks":"Provvederemo a correggerli quanto prima.","technical_details":"Illustralo in dettaglio per consentirci di trovare una soluzione.","other_question":"Cosa desideri segnalarci?","other_desc":"Tieni presente che non possiamo trattare questioni o reclami specifici riguardanti gli affari o le politiche dell'UE. ","other_presence":"Ci limitiamo a ottimizzare gli aspetti digitali della presenza online della Commissione.","help_us":"Aiutaci a rispondere meglio alle tue esigenze specificando i problemi che hai incontrato.","information_not_found":"impossibile trovare le informazioni ricercate","technical_issue":"problema tecnico","spot_mistake":"errori nel testo","what_problem":"Quale problema hai incontrato?","error_other":"Altro","submit_feedback":"Invia feedback","thank_you_message":"Grazie per il feedback!","message_error_request":"Si \u00e8 verificato un errore e non abbiamo potuto ricevere i tuoi commenti. Si prega di riprovare.","message_error_fields":"Compilare tutti i campi a eccezione di quelli facoltativi.","close":"Chiudi","tell_us":"Specifica il problema che hai riscontrato:","other":"altro","field_mandatory":"Questo campo \u00e8 obbligatorio","personal_information":"Non includere informazioni personali nei commenti."},"lv":{"rate_this":"Nov\u0113rt\u0113t \u0161o lapu","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"vai <link>sniegt atsauksmi<\/link>","remaining":"Atliku\u0161ais rakstz\u012bmju skaits","need_help":"Neizdodas atrast inform\u0101ciju?","europe_direct":"<link>Jums var pal\u012bdz\u0113t dienests \u201cEurope Direct\u201d<\/link> (saite atv\u0113rsies jaun\u0101 ciln\u0113).","website_help":"Vai uzskat\u0101t, ka inform\u0101cija \u0161aj\u0101 vietn\u0113 vai lap\u0101 nav piln\u012bga? Iesakiet, kas mums v\u0113l b\u016btu j\u0101pievieno.","mistake_notice":"L\u016bdzu, zi\u0146ojiet par paman\u012btaj\u0101m k\u013c\u016bd\u0101m!","mistake_thanks":"M\u0113s t\u0101s iesp\u0113jami dr\u012bz izlabosim.","technical_details":"L\u016bdzu, aprakstiet probl\u0113mu p\u0113c iesp\u0113jas s\u012bk\u0101k\u00a0\u2013 tas mums pal\u012bdz\u0113s to \u0101tr\u0101k nov\u0113rst.","other_question":"Vai v\u0113laties mums ko vaic\u0101t vai pazi\u0146ot?","other_desc":"L\u016bdzu, \u0146emiet v\u0113r\u0101, ka m\u0113s nesniedzam atbildes uz jaut\u0101jumiem par ES liet\u0101m un politiku. ","other_presence":"M\u016bsu darbs ir optimiz\u0113t Komisijas t\u012bmek\u013cviet\u0146u digit\u0101los aspektus.","help_us":"Pal\u012bdziet mums lapu uzlabot \u2014 past\u0101siet, k\u0101das probl\u0113mas jums rad\u0101s!","information_not_found":"Neatradu vajadz\u012bgo inform\u0101ciju","technical_issue":"Tehniska probl\u0113ma","spot_mistake":"K\u013c\u016bda(-s) tekst\u0101","what_problem":"Vai kaut kas nedarbojas, k\u0101 vajadz\u0113tu?","error_other":"Cita","submit_feedback":"Nos\u016bt\u012bt atsauksmi","thank_you_message":"Paldies par atsauksmi!","message_error_request":"Rad\u0101s k\u013c\u016bda, l\u012bdz ar to j\u016bsu atsauksmi neesam sa\u0146\u0113mu\u0161i. M\u0113\u0123iniet v\u0113lreiz!","message_error_fields":"Aizpildiet visus laukus (varat neaizpild\u012bt tikai tos, par kuriem teikts, ka tie nav oblig\u0101ti).","close":"Aizv\u0113rt","tell_us":"K\u0101da probl\u0113ma jums rad\u0101s?","other":"Cita","field_mandatory":"\u0160is lauks j\u0101aizpilda oblig\u0101ti","personal_information":"L\u016bdzam koment\u0101ros neiek\u013caut personas datus."},"lt":{"rate_this":"\u012evertinkite \u0161\u012f puslap\u012f","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"arba <link>pateikite mums daugiau pastab\u0173<\/link>","remaining":"\u017eenkl\u0173 limitas","need_help":"Reikia pagalbos atliekant paie\u0161k\u0105?","europe_direct":"<link>Jums gali pad\u0117ti \u201eEurope Direct\u201c<\/link> (atveriama nauja kortel\u0117).","website_help":"Manote, kad \u0161ioje svetain\u0117je arba \u0161iame puslapyje tr\u016bksta informacijos? Sakykite, k\u0105 tur\u0117tume papildyti.","mistake_notice":"Ar galite pateikti daugiau informacijos apie pasteb\u0117t\u0105\u00a0(-as) klaid\u0105\u00a0(-as)?","mistake_thanks":"Klaid\u0105\u00a0(-as) i\u0161taisysime kuo grei\u010diau.","technical_details":"Pateikite kuo daugiau informacijos, kad problem\u0105 gal\u0117tume i\u0161spr\u0119sti.","other_question":"Kuo nor\u0117tum\u0117te pasidalyti su mumis?","other_desc":"D\u0117mesio! Negalime nagrin\u0117ti konkre\u010di\u0173 klausim\u0173 ar skund\u0173, susijusi\u0173 su ES reikalais arba politika. ","other_presence":"M\u016bs\u0173 tikslas \u2013 tiesiog optimizuoti skaitmeninius Komisijos interneto svetaini\u0173 aspektus.","help_us":"Pad\u0117kite mums tobulinti \u0161\u012f puslap\u012f, kad juo naudotis b\u016bt\u0173 patogiau \u2013 apra\u0161ykite i\u0161kilusias problemas.","information_not_found":"nerandu reikiamos informacijos","technical_issue":"technin\u0117 problema","spot_mistake":"klaida\u00a0(-os) tekste","what_problem":"Kokia problema i\u0161kilo?","error_other":"Kita","submit_feedback":"Si\u0173sti atsiliepim\u0105","thank_you_message":"D\u0117kojame u\u017e atsiliepim\u0105!","message_error_request":"\u012evyko klaida ir j\u016bs\u0173 atsiliepimo negavome. Pabandykite dar kart\u0105.","message_error_fields":"U\u017epildykite visus laukelius, nebent jie b\u016bt\u0173 pa\u017eym\u0117ti kaip neprivalomi.","close":"U\u017edaryti","tell_us":"Nurodykite, kokia problema kilo:","other":"kita","field_mandatory":"\u0160is laukelis privalomas","personal_information":"Savo komentaruose nenurodykite joki\u0173 asmens duomen\u0173."},"hu":{"rate_this":"K\u00e9rj\u00fck, \u00e9rt\u00e9kelje a webhelyet","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"vagy <link>\u00edrja meg \u00e9szrev\u00e9teleit<\/link>","remaining":"karakter haszn\u00e1lhat\u00f3 m\u00e9g fel","need_help":"Seg\u00edts\u00e9gre van sz\u00fcks\u00e9ge ahhoz, hogy megtal\u00e1lja a keresett inform\u00e1ci\u00f3t?","europe_direct":"<link>Forduljon a Europe Direct<\/link> munkat\u00e1rsaihoz (a link \u00faj lapon ny\u00edlik meg).","website_help":"\u00d6n szerint hi\u00e1nyoznak inform\u00e1ci\u00f3k err\u0151l a webhelyr\u0151l? Mit aj\u00e1nl, mivel b\u0151v\u00edts\u00fck a tartalmat?","mistake_notice":"Tudn\u00e1-e pontos\u00edtani, milyen hib\u00e1(ka)t \u00e9szlelt?","mistake_thanks":"Igyeksz\u00fcnk a hib\u00e1(ka)t mihamarabb kijav\u00edtani.","technical_details":"K\u00e9rj\u00fck, ismertesse min\u00e9l r\u00e9szletesebben az esetet, hogy a lehet\u0151 leggyorsabban megoldhassuk a probl\u00e9m\u00e1t.","other_question":"K\u00e9rj\u00fck, fejtse ki, milyen probl\u00e9m\u00e1t \u00e9szlelt.","other_desc":"Felh\u00edvjuk figyelm\u00e9t, hogy uni\u00f3s \u00fcgyekhez vagy szakpolitik\u00e1khoz kapcsol\u00f3d\u00f3 konkr\u00e9t k\u00e9rd\u00e9sekkel vagy panaszokkal nem \u00e1ll m\u00f3dunkban foglalkozni. ","other_presence":"Feladatunk az, hogy az Eur\u00f3pai Bizotts\u00e1g online jelenl\u00e9t\u00e9t digit\u00e1lis szempontb\u00f3l optimaliz\u00e1ljuk.","help_us":"Seg\u00edtsen nek\u00fcnk, hogy jav\u00edthassuk a felhaszn\u00e1l\u00f3i \u00e9lm\u00e9nyt \u2013 ossza meg vel\u00fcnk az \u00d6n \u00e1ltal tapasztalt probl\u00e9m\u00e1kat.","information_not_found":"Nem tal\u00e1lom a keresett inform\u00e1ci\u00f3t","technical_issue":"Technikai probl\u00e9ma","spot_mistake":"Hiba (hib\u00e1k) a tartalomban","what_problem":"Miben \u00e1ll a probl\u00e9ma?","error_other":"Egy\u00e9b","submit_feedback":"Visszajelz\u00e9s beny\u00fajt\u00e1sa","thank_you_message":"K\u00f6sz\u00f6nj\u00fck visszajelz\u00e9s\u00e9t!","message_error_request":"Hiba t\u00f6rt\u00e9nt a visszajelz\u00e9s tov\u00e1bb\u00edt\u00e1sakor. K\u00e9rj\u00fck, pr\u00f3b\u00e1lja meg \u00fajra.","message_error_fields":"K\u00e9rj\u00fck, t\u00f6ltse ki az \u00f6sszes mez\u0151t, amely nincs fakultat\u00edvk\u00e9nt megjel\u00f6lve.","close":"Bez\u00e1r\u00e1s","tell_us":"K\u00e9rj\u00fck, ismertesse, milyen probl\u00e9m\u00e1ba \u00fctk\u00f6z\u00f6tt:","other":"Egy\u00e9b","field_mandatory":"A mez\u0151 kit\u00f6lt\u00e9se k\u00f6telez\u0151","personal_information":"K\u00e9rj\u00fck, ne t\u00fcntessen fel szem\u00e9lyes adatokat a visszajelz\u00e9s\u00e9ben."},"mt":{"rate_this":"Ag\u0127ti l-opinjoni tieg\u0127ek dwar din il-pa\u0121na","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"jew <link>ag\u0127tina aktar feedback<\/link>","remaining":"karattri li fadallek:","need_help":"G\u0127andek b\u017conn l-g\u0127ajnuna biex issib dak li qed tfittex?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> jista\u2019 jg\u0127inek (jinfeta\u0127 f\u2019tab \u0121dida).","website_help":"T\u0127oss li hemm informazzjoni nieqsa f\u2019dan is-sit jew f\u2019din il-pa\u0121na? G\u0127idilna x\u2019g\u0127andna n\u017cidu.","mistake_notice":"Tista\u2019 tag\u0127ti aktar dettalji dwar l-i\u017cbalji li nnotajt?","mistake_thanks":"Se nikkore\u0121u l-i\u017cbalji malajr kemm jista\u2019 jkun.","technical_details":"Jekk jog\u0127\u0121bok ipprovdi kemm jista\u2019 jkun dettalji sabiex inkunu nistg\u0127u nsolvu l-kwistjoni.","other_question":"X\u2019tixtieq taqsam mag\u0127na?","other_desc":"Jekk jog\u0127\u0121bok kun af li ma nistg\u0127ux nittrattaw mistoqsijiet jew ilmenti spe\u010bifi\u010bi dwar l-affarijiet jew il-politiki tal-UE. ","other_presence":"Il-\u0127idma tag\u0127na g\u0127andha l-g\u0127an sempli\u010biment li tottimizza l-aspetti di\u0121itali tal-pre\u017cenza online tal-Kummissjoni.","help_us":"G\u0127inna ntejbu l-esperjenza tieg\u0127ek \u2013 g\u0127idilna kwalunkwe problema li kellek.","information_not_found":"Ma nistax insib l-informazzjoni li g\u0127andi b\u017conn","technical_issue":"Kwistjoni teknika","spot_mistake":"\u017bbalji fit-test","what_problem":"X\u2019jidher li hija l-problema?","error_other":"O\u0127rajn","submit_feedback":"Ibg\u0127at il-feedback","thank_you_message":"Grazzi tal-feedback!","message_error_request":"Se\u0127\u0127 \u017cball u ma stajniex nir\u010bievu l-feedback tieg\u0127ek. Jekk jog\u0127\u0121bok er\u0121a' pprova.","message_error_fields":"Jekk jog\u0127\u0121bok imla l-oqsma kollha, sakemm ma jkunux immarkati b\u0127ala fakultattivi.","close":"Ag\u0127laq","tell_us":"G\u0127idilna xi problema kellek:","other":"O\u0127rajn","field_mandatory":"Dan il-qasam huwa obbligatorju","personal_information":"Jekk jog\u0127\u0121bok tinkludix informazzjoni personali fil-kummenti tieg\u0127ek."},"nl":{"rate_this":"Beoordeel deze pagina","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"of <link>geef ons meer feedback<\/link>","remaining":"tekens over","need_help":"Hebt u hulp nodig om te vinden wat u zoekt?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> kan u daarbij helpen (opent in een nieuw tabblad).","website_help":"Vindt u dat er op deze site of op deze pagina informatie ontbreekt? Vertel ons wat we moeten toevoegen.","mistake_notice":"Kunt u meer details geven over de door u opgemerkte fout(en)?","mistake_thanks":"Wij zullen de fout(en) zo spoedig mogelijk corrigeren.","technical_details":"Geef zoveel mogelijk details om het probleem op te lossen.","other_question":"Wat wilt u met ons delen?","other_desc":"Wij kunnen geen specifieke vragen of klachten over EU-aangelegenheden of -beleid behandelen. ","other_presence":"Met ons werk willen wij gewoon de onlineaanwezigheid van de Commissie in al haar digitale aspecten optimaliseren.","help_us":"Help ons en vertel ons waarom niet.","information_not_found":"Ik kon niet vinden wat ik zocht","technical_issue":"technische vraag","spot_mistake":"fout(en) in de tekst","what_problem":"Wat is volgens u het probleem?","error_other":"Ander probleem","submit_feedback":"Mijn feedback indienen","thank_you_message":"Bedankt voor uw feedback!","message_error_request":"Er is iets misgegaan: we hebben uw feedback niet ontvangen. Probeer het opnieuw.","message_error_fields":"Vul alle velden in te vullen, behalve als erbij staat dat ze niet verplicht zijn.","close":"Sluiten","tell_us":"Vertel ons welk probleem u hebt ondervonden:","other":"ander","field_mandatory":"Dit veld is verplicht","personal_information":"Gelieve in uw opmerkingen geen persoonsgegevens te vermelden."},"pl":{"rate_this":"Oce\u0144 t\u0119 stron\u0119","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"lub <link>przeka\u017c nam swoje uwagi<\/link>","remaining":"Pozosta\u0142o znak\u00f3w:","need_help":"Nie znajdujesz potrzebnych Ci informacji?","europe_direct":"Pomo\u017ce Ci serwis <link>Europe Direct<\/link> (strona otworzy si\u0119 w nowym oknie).","website_help":"Uwa\u017casz, \u017ce w portalu lub na tej stronie brakuje okre\u015blonych informacji? Napisz, jakie informacje powinni\u015bmy doda\u0107.","mistake_notice":"Prosimy o wskazanie zauwa\u017conych b\u0142\u0119d\u00f3w.","mistake_thanks":"Poprawimy je jak najszybciej.","technical_details":"Prosimy o szczeg\u00f3\u0142owy opis, aby\u015bmy mogli rozwi\u0105za\u0107 ten problem.","other_question":"Jakie uwagi chcesz nam przekaza\u0107?","other_desc":"Niestety, nie jeste\u015bmy w stanie odpowiedzie\u0107 na konkretne pytania lub skargi dotycz\u0105ce dzia\u0142a\u0144 lub polityki UE. ","other_presence":"Naszym zadaniem jest ulepszenie stron internetowych Komisji.","help_us":"Pom\u00f3\u017c nam ulepszy\u0107 t\u0119 stron\u0119 \u2013 zg\u0142o\u015b nam ewentualne problemy.","information_not_found":"Nie mog\u0119 znale\u017a\u0107 informacji, kt\u00f3rych potrzebuj\u0119","technical_issue":"Problem techniczny","spot_mistake":"B\u0142\u0119dy w tek\u015bcie","what_problem":"Na czym polega problem?","error_other":"Inne","submit_feedback":"Wy\u015blij uwagi","thank_you_message":"Dzi\u0119kujemy za ocen\u0119!","message_error_request":"Wyst\u0105pi\u0142 b\u0142\u0105d i nie otrzymali\u015bmy twoich uwag. Spr\u00f3buj ponownie.","message_error_fields":"Prosz\u0119 wype\u0142ni\u0107 wszystkie pola, chyba \u017ce s\u0105 one oznaczone jako opcjonalne.","close":"Zamknij","tell_us":"Napotkany przez Ciebie problem:","other":"Inne","field_mandatory":"To pole jest obowi\u0105zkowe","personal_information":"W komentarzach nie nale\u017cy podawa\u0107 \u017cadnych danych osobowych."},"pt":{"rate_this":"Avalie esta p\u00e1gina","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"ou <link>d\u00ea-nos a sua opini\u00e3o<\/link>","remaining":"carateres restantes","need_help":"Precisa de ajuda para encontrar o que procura?","europe_direct":"<link>O Europe Direct<\/link> pode ajud\u00e1-lo (abre num novo separador).","website_help":"Considera que faltam informa\u00e7\u00f5es neste s\u00edtio ou nesta p\u00e1gina? Diga-nos que informa\u00e7\u00f5es devemos acrescentar.","mistake_notice":"Pode-nos dar mais pormenores sobre o(s) erro(s) que detetou?","mistake_thanks":"Corrigiremos o(s) erro(s) logo que poss\u00edvel.","technical_details":"Forne\u00e7a todos os pormenores poss\u00edveis para que possamos resolver o problema.","other_question":"O que gostaria de partilhar connosco?","other_desc":"Tenha em conta que n\u00e3o podemos tratar quest\u00f5es ou queixas espec\u00edficas sobre assuntos ou pol\u00edticas da UE. ","other_presence":"O objetivo do nosso trabalho \u00e9 apenas otimizar os aspetos digitais da presen\u00e7a em linha da Comiss\u00e3o.","help_us":"Ajude-nos a melhorar a sua experi\u00eancia \u2014 diga-nos se teve algum problema.","information_not_found":"N\u00e3o consigo encontrar as informa\u00e7\u00f5es de que preciso","technical_issue":"Quest\u00e3o t\u00e9cnica","spot_mistake":"Erro(s) no texto","what_problem":"Qual \u00e9 o problema?","error_other":"Outro","submit_feedback":"Enviar coment\u00e1rios","thank_you_message":"Agradecemos os seus coment\u00e1rios!","message_error_request":"Ocorreu um erro e n\u00e3o conseguimos receber os seus coment\u00e1rios. Volte a tentar.","message_error_fields":"Preencha todos os campos, a menos que estejam assinalados como facultativos.","close":"Fechar","tell_us":"Comunique-nos o problema que teve:","other":"Outro","field_mandatory":"Este campo \u00e9 obrigat\u00f3rio","personal_information":"N\u00e3o inclua informa\u00e7\u00f5es pessoais nos seus coment\u00e1rios."},"ro":{"rate_this":"Evalua\u021bi pagina","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"sau <link>da\u021bi-ne mai multe detalii<\/link>","remaining":"caractere r\u0103mase","need_help":"Ave\u021bi nevoie de ajutor pentru a g\u0103si ce c\u0103uta\u021bi?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> v\u0103 poate ajuta (se deschide \u00eentr-o fil\u0103 nou\u0103).","website_help":"Considera\u021bi c\u0103 lipsesc informa\u021bii pe acest site sau pe aceast\u0103 pagin\u0103? Spune\u021bi-ne ce ar trebui s\u0103 ad\u0103ug\u0103m.","mistake_notice":"Pute\u021bi oferi mai multe detalii cu privire la gre\u0219eala  sau gre\u0219elile pe care le-a\u021bi observat?","mistake_thanks":"Vom corecta gre\u0219eala (gre\u0219elile) c\u00e2t mai cur\u00e2nd posibil.","technical_details":"V\u0103 rug\u0103m s\u0103 furniza\u021bi c\u00e2t mai multe detalii, astfel \u00eenc\u00e2t s\u0103 o putem rezolva c\u00e2t mai repede.","other_question":"Ce a\u021bi dori s\u0103 ne \u00eemp\u0103rt\u0103\u0219i\u021bi?","other_desc":"Preciz\u0103m c\u0103 nu putem trata \u00eentreb\u0103ri sau pl\u00e2ngeri specifice privind afacerile sau politicile UE. ","other_presence":"Activitatea noastr\u0103 urm\u0103re\u0219te pur \u0219i simplu s\u0103 optimizeze aspectele digitale ale prezen\u021bei online a Comisiei.","help_us":"Pentru a v\u0103 oferi o experien\u021b\u0103 c\u00e2t mai pozitiv\u0103, ne-ar ajuta dac\u0103 ne-a\u021bi comunica eventualele probleme pe care le-a\u021bi \u00eent\u00e2mpinat.","information_not_found":"Nu g\u0103sesc informa\u021biile de care am nevoie","technical_issue":"Problem\u0103 tehnic\u0103","spot_mistake":"Gre\u0219eal\u0103 (gre\u0219eli) \u00een text","what_problem":"Despre ce problem\u0103 este vorba?","error_other":"Alt\u0103 problem\u0103","submit_feedback":"Trimite observa\u021biile mele","thank_you_message":"V\u0103 mul\u021bumim pentru observa\u021bii!","message_error_request":"Din cauza unei erori nu am fost \u00een m\u0103sur\u0103 s\u0103 primim observa\u021biile dumneavoastr\u0103. V\u0103 rug\u0103m s\u0103 \u00eencerca\u021bi din nou.","message_error_fields":"V\u0103 rug\u0103m s\u0103 completa\u021bi toate c\u00e2mpurile obligatorii (cele op\u021bionale sunt marcate ca atare).","close":"\u00cenchide\u021bi","tell_us":"Spune\u021bi-ne cu ce problem\u0103 v-a\u021bi confruntat:","other":"Altele","field_mandatory":"Acest c\u00e2mp este obligatoriu","personal_information":"V\u0103 rug\u0103m s\u0103 nu include\u021bi informa\u021bii personale \u00een c\u00e2mpul de text liber."},"sk":{"rate_this":"Ohodno\u0165te t\u00fato webov\u00fa str\u00e1nku","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"alebo <link>n\u00e1m poskytnite sp\u00e4tn\u00fa v\u00e4zbu<\/link>","remaining":"zost\u00e1vaj\u00face znaky","need_help":"Potrebujete pomoc pri h\u013eadan\u00ed inform\u00e1ci\u00ed?","europe_direct":"<link>Slu\u017eba Europe Direct<\/link> v\u00e1m s t\u00fdm m\u00f4\u017ee pom\u00f4c\u0165 (otvor\u00ed sa na novej karte).","website_help":"Domnievate sa, \u017ee na tomto s\u00eddle alebo na tejto str\u00e1nke ch\u00fdbaj\u00fa inform\u00e1cie? Dajte n\u00e1m vedie\u0165, \u010do by sme mali doplni\u0165.","mistake_notice":"M\u00f4\u017eete podrobnej\u0161ie op\u00edsa\u0165 chyby, ktor\u00e9 ste si v\u0161imli?","mistake_thanks":"Chybu(-y) oprav\u00edme \u010do najsk\u00f4r.","technical_details":"Uve\u010fte \u010do najviac podrobnost\u00ed, aby sme mohli probl\u00e9m vyrie\u0161i\u0165.","other_question":"O \u010do by ste sa s nami chceli podeli\u0165?","other_desc":"Upozor\u0148ujeme, \u017ee nem\u00f4\u017eeme rie\u0161i\u0165 konkr\u00e9tne ot\u00e1zky alebo s\u0165a\u017enosti t\u00fdkaj\u00face sa z\u00e1le\u017eitost\u00ed alebo polit\u00edk E\u00da. ","other_presence":"Cie\u013eom na\u0161ej pr\u00e1ce je len optimalizova\u0165 digit\u00e1lnu prezent\u00e1ciu Komisie na internete.","help_us":"Pom\u00f4\u017ete n\u00e1m vylep\u0161i\u0165 na\u0161e slu\u017eby \u2014 povedzte n\u00e1m o va\u0161om probl\u00e9me.","information_not_found":"Neviem n\u00e1js\u0165 inform\u00e1cie, ktor\u00e9 potrebujem","technical_issue":"Technick\u00fd probl\u00e9m","spot_mistake":"Chyba(-y) v texte","what_problem":"S ak\u00fdm probl\u00e9mom ste sa stretli?","error_other":"In\u00e9","submit_feedback":"Odo\u0161lite sp\u00e4tn\u00fa v\u00e4zbu","thank_you_message":"\u010eakujeme v\u00e1m za sp\u00e4tn\u00fa v\u00e4zbu!","message_error_request":"Vyskytla sa chyba a va\u0161u sp\u00e4tn\u00fa v\u00e4zbu sme nedostali. Sk\u00faste to znova.","message_error_fields":"Vypl\u0148te v\u0161etky pol\u00ed\u010dka, pokia\u013e nie s\u00fa ozna\u010den\u00e9 ako nepovinn\u00e9.","close":"Zavrie\u0165","tell_us":"Povedzte n\u00e1m, s\u00a0ak\u00fd probl\u00e9mom ste stretli:","other":"In\u00e9","field_mandatory":"Toto pole je povinn\u00e9","personal_information":"V koment\u00e1roch neuv\u00e1dzajte \u017eiadne osobn\u00e9 \u00fadaje."},"sl":{"rate_this":"Ocenite to stran","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"ali <link>povejte svoje mnenje<\/link>","remaining":"\u0161tevilo preostalih znakov","need_help":"Potrebujete pomo\u010d?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> vam lahko pomaga (odpre se v novem zavihku).","website_help":"Ali menite, da na tem spleti\u0161\u010du ali tej strani ni dolo\u010denih informacij? Povejte nam, kaj bi morali dodati.","mistake_notice":"Ali lahko navedete ve\u010d informacij o napaki, ki ste jo opazili?","mistake_thanks":"Napako bomo sku\u0161ali \u010dim prej odpraviti.","technical_details":"Navedite \u010dim ve\u010d podrobnosti, da jo bomo lahko \u010dim prej odpravili.","other_question":"Kaj \u017eelite deliti z nami?","other_desc":"Upo\u0161tevajte, da ne moremo odgovoriti na specifi\u010dna vpra\u0161anja ali obravnavati prito\u017eb v zvezi z zadevami ali politikami EU. ","other_presence":"Na\u0161e delo je namenjeno zgolj optimizaciji digitalnih vidikov spletne prisotnosti Komisije.","help_us":"Pomagajte nam izbolj\u0161ati stran. Sporo\u010dite nam, na kak\u0161ne te\u017eave ste naleteli.","information_not_found":"Ne najdem potrebnih informacij","technical_issue":"Tehni\u010dna te\u017eava","spot_mistake":"Napaka(-e) v besedilu","what_problem":"Za kak\u0161no te\u017eavo gre?","error_other":"Drugo","submit_feedback":"Po\u0161lji povratne informacije","thank_you_message":"Hvala za va\u0161e mnenje.","message_error_request":"Pri\u0161lo je do napake, zato va\u0161ih povratnih informacij nismo prejeli. Poskusite znova.","message_error_fields":"Izpolnite vsa polja, razen \u010de so ozna\u010dena kot neobvezna.","close":"Zapri","tell_us":"Navedite, kak\u0161no te\u017eavo ste imeli.","other":"Drugo","field_mandatory":"To polje je obvezno","personal_information":"Prosimo, da v svojih pripombah ne navajate nobenih osebnih podatkov."},"fi":{"rate_this":"Arvioi t\u00e4m\u00e4 sivu","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"tai <link>anna tarkempaa palautetta<\/link>","remaining":"merkki\u00e4 j\u00e4ljell\u00e4","need_help":"Tarvitsetko apua tiedonhakuun?","europe_direct":"<link>Europe Direct<\/link> voi auttaa (sivu avautuu linkist\u00e4 uudelle v\u00e4lilehdelle).","website_help":"Puuttuuko t\u00e4lt\u00e4 sivulta tai sivustolta mielest\u00e4si jotakin tietoa? Kerro, mit\u00e4 tietoa olisi lis\u00e4tt\u00e4v\u00e4.","mistake_notice":"Kerro, mit\u00e4 virheit\u00e4 havaitsit.","mistake_thanks":"Korjaamme virheet mahdollisimman pian.","technical_details":"Anna mahdollisimman tarkat tiedot, jotta voimme ratkaista ongelman.","other_question":"Mit\u00e4 palautetta haluaisit antaa?","other_desc":"Huomaa, ettemme voi vastata EU:n toimiin tai politiikkaan liittyviin kysymyksiin. ","other_presence":"T\u00e4ll\u00e4 palautekyselyll\u00e4 halutaan vain parantaa komission verkkosivuja ja niiden toimintaa.","help_us":"Auta parantamaan sivuston k\u00e4ytt\u00f6kokemusta \u2013 kerro meille mahdollisista ongelmista.","information_not_found":"En l\u00f6yd\u00e4 hakemaani tietoa","technical_issue":"Tekninen ongelma","spot_mistake":"Tekstiss\u00e4 on virheit\u00e4","what_problem":"Millainen ongelma sivustolla esiintyi?","error_other":"Muu","submit_feedback":"L\u00e4het\u00e4 palaute","thank_you_message":"Kiitos palautteesta!","message_error_request":"Virhe \u2013 palautteen l\u00e4hetys ei onnistunut. Yrit\u00e4 uudelleen.","message_error_fields":"T\u00e4yt\u00e4 kaikki pakolliset kent\u00e4t.","close":"Sulje","tell_us":"Kerro havaitsemastasi ongelmasta:","other":"Muu","field_mandatory":"Pakollinen kentt\u00e4","personal_information":"\u00c4l\u00e4 sis\u00e4llyt\u00e4 kommentteihisi mit\u00e4\u00e4n henkil\u00f6tietoja."},"sv":{"rate_this":"Betygs\u00e4tt sidan","choose_rate":"Choose a rating from 1 to 5","star":"star","stars":"stars","give_us":"eller <link>l\u00e4mna fler synpunkter<\/link>","remaining":"tecken kvar","need_help":"Beh\u00f6ver du hj\u00e4lp att hitta vad du letar efter?","europe_direct":"<link>Europa direkt<\/link> kan hj\u00e4lpa dig (l\u00e4nken \u00f6ppnas i en ny flik).","website_help":"Tycker du att det saknas information p\u00e5 webbplatsen eller sidan? Vad b\u00f6r vi l\u00e4gga till?","mistake_notice":"Vilka fel uppt\u00e4ckte du?","mistake_thanks":"Vi r\u00e4ttar till dem s\u00e5 fort som m\u00f6jligt.","technical_details":"Beskriv s\u00e5 ing\u00e5ende som m\u00f6jligt s\u00e5 att vi kan l\u00f6sa problemet.","other_question":"Vilka synpunkter vill du framf\u00f6ra?","other_desc":"T\u00e4nk p\u00e5 att vi inte kan svara p\u00e5 specifika fr\u00e5gor eller klagom\u00e5l om EU-fr\u00e5gor eller EU-politik. ","other_presence":"Vi arbetar bara med att f\u00f6rb\u00e4ttra kommissionens webbplatser.","help_us":"Hj\u00e4lp oss att f\u00f6rb\u00e4ttra webbplatsen \u2013 ber\u00e4tta vilka problem du haft.","information_not_found":"Jag hittar inte den information jag beh\u00f6ver","technical_issue":"Tekniskt problem","spot_mistake":"Fel i texten","what_problem":"Vad \u00e4r problemet?","error_other":"Annat","submit_feedback":"Skicka mina synpunkter","thank_you_message":"Tack f\u00f6r dina synpunkter!","message_error_request":"Det har uppst\u00e5tt ett fel. Vi kunde inte ta emot dina synpunkter. F\u00f6rs\u00f6k igen.","message_error_fields":"Fyll i alla f\u00e4lt om de inte \u00e4r markerade som frivilliga.","close":"St\u00e4ng","tell_us":"Vilka problem st\u00f6tte du p\u00e5?","other":"Annat","field_mandatory":"Detta f\u00e4lt \u00e4r obligatoriskt","personal_information":"L\u00e4mna inga personuppgifter i dina kommentarer."}}},!0)
